We're getting married.
What about Dad? Leo is on my side.
Then why didn't he tell you
about me Marsha?
Because he knew,
and he never said a word to you.
It's not often that I'm grateful for
the fact that I've got no family.
I want you to be protected.
If Benjamin's intentions are good,
he won't object.
I'm starting to wonder whether
this is just some way
of getting back at Ted.
Why today? Because of her.
This has nothing to do with Julia!
LOW CHATTER
BIRDSONG
Everything's upside down.
Our happy family...
..the one I remember,
it doesn't exist any more.
Mum.
Dad.
And it's all down to one person.
Remove him...
..remove the problem.
JULIA GIGGLES
Can I help you?
I hope so.
I'm looking for Benjamin.
Sorry, and, er...you are...?
I'm his brother.
LEO LAUGHS
What are the chances of getting
a little sliver of cake
before he gets back?
JULIA CHUCKLES
You're not having any.
Meanie. Benjamin.
There's someone to see you.
Kieran.
Mum, this is,
er...Benjamin's brother.
Half.
My...my half-brother.
Half, whole,
it's all the same thing.
I'm sorry to just turn up.
I could have sworn you told us that
Benjamin was an only child, Mum.
Oh, you must have it, er...confused.
It's lovely to meet you. I'm Julia.
Kieran. It's nice to meet you too.
So, how you been?
Is this your wife?
STIFLED LAUGHTER
Er...not so much...
Julia is my...
We...we're getting married.
Oh, well, it's even nicer
to meet you, then.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Kieran here's a bit late to the
party, wouldn't you say, Benjamin?
Well, we...we haven't seen
each other in a while.
Define "a while."
17 years, give or take.
Well, that's...that's...that's
biblical.
What happened?
Just...
..one of those things.
That's a detailed explanation.
Come on, why don't we, er...get
some privacy?
Give us a chance to...catch up.
Give him a hug, then.
Poor bloke's come all this way.
From somewhere very far from Kent,
by the sounds of things.
We should sing.
Er...Della, would you help me
light the candles?
Are you seriously
going to pretend...
..that that didn't just happen?
I'm not pretending anything.
I have to be honest, Mum, I've
never heard mention of his brother.
Well, why would you have?
You can barely bring yourself to
exchange pleasantries with Benjamin.
Either way, it's hardly
the most attractive of qualities,
not speaking to your brother
for half your life.
It's kind of...psychopathic.
It's not always easy...family.
Delicately done.
Why can't you just think first,
engage your mouth second?
The man is a liar, end of!
So, this is your solution -
to leave?
I'm done trying to tell Mum things
she doesn't want to hear.
I've got my own family
to worry about.
Newsflash - we're your family too!
MESSAGE ALERT
You're not going to believe this,
but... Oh!
Patrick goes and you follow. Nice.
Two words, bro, and they're words
you won't recognise -
insufficient funds.
I can't turn down a free lift home.
Anyway, you don't want to spend
your birthday night with your dry,
old siblings.
No, you're right,
I can't think of anything worse.
Yeah.
See you.
DOOR OPENS
Happy birthday, Leo Lion!
Rawr!
She rides well, doesn't she?
She's, er...she's great.
Oh, you haven't scratched it
already?
No, that...that was Patrick.
So, along with lunch,
you've also missed out on
the latest absurdity
with our resident toy boy.
I'm thinking you, me,
birthday dinner at The Oak,
I'll regale you the story,
you keep my glass filled up...
..everyone's happy.
I-I think we've got him this time,
Dad.
I can't say it again. No more
Benjamin, no more your mother.
It's all...
HE SIGHS
It's not good for me.
There's still time to stop
this wedding. We could...
Be quiet, Leo.
Remember whose house this is.
Dinner, the two of us, sounds great.
Just not tonight.
Sure, whenever. Just...
Patrick's having an affair.
Like father, like son, I guess.
No, that's different.
He wasn't just bored or randy,
like my shit of an older brother,
he was...lost.
I mean, you work all your life
and you give everything you have
and then it's just, like,
boom, retirement.
So...all that doing the right thing
comes to nothing.
So, when the wrong thing
presents itself...
Did you just describe my mother
as the wrong thing?
Well, she produced you,
which I consider one of her
more redeeming features,
but, then, she did split up
my parents.
Who were both faultless, right?
So, if it wasn't for the witchery
of my mother,
they'd still be together?
Yep.
And thriving.
We'd all be.
Well, you might be able to
test your theory soon.
Don't just say that, then go
all Coy Roy. What do you mean?
I mean...they're sleeping
in separate beds.
The kiss of death.
So, maybe there's a way.
With a little helping hand.
Don't look at me.
HE SIGHS
You do realise that if our 'rents
weren't together...
..there'd be none of this
icky pseudo-stepkids' vibe...
..and we could...we could be
more open?
History has a funny way
of repeating itself.
The same mistakes made again
and again.
DOOR SLAMS SHUT
Ending up with me trapped
in something I don't want to be in.
With a man I can't trust.
FOOTSTEPS
SHE EXHALES
KNOCK AT DOOR
Kieran...
..he's, er...he's going to stay
at The Oak.
You told me that you were
an only child.
And you made me stand
in front of them,
in front of all of them, and lie.
You didn't have to.
You think my kids need
any more excuse to go against us?
No. No, look...look, I know...I know
that they don't...
I know that they don't,
and I...and...and I can explain,
but...but first, you...you
just have to believe, I...
It's the size of it that upsets me,
because it's not a small thing,
is it?
It's not something that I can
just... It's... H-He's...
He's your family,
he's your flesh and blood.
And if you can lie about that,
you can lie about anything.
Er...
You have to understand...
..I've...I've spent my whole life
trying to get away from...
..him. From...from the...the past.
And when I came down to London, it
meant that I could be who I wanted,
I could SAY what I wanted!
So, I just...I ended up
telling people the easiest thing!
That I'm an only child.
And the more I said it, the m...
Well, the more it stopped
being a lie
and just became normal.
And...and so then I-I met you
and you were just so clever
and...and...and cultured,
and I just wanted to keep up!
Right. So, it's on me, then?
No. No! No, it's not!
You...you...you wouldn't understand.
You...couldn't!
That level of...of shame,
of just wanting to claw at
your own skin
until you just don't exist any more!
I didn't have a choice, OK?
I-I-I did it to...survive.
And what does he want from you?
Um...
I-I think he wants to...
I think he wants to show me
that he's changed. Huh!
SHE CHUCKLES SOFTLY
And you, what do you want?
I want you not...not to look at me
like that.
Like what?
Like...like I've broken something.
I...
I can fix this!
I can fix it. Cos I am not...I am
not letting you go!
Do you understand?
I'm not letting you go!
Cos you are...you are EVERYTHING!
You are everything! Everything!
Then why risk it?
What were you so ashamed of?
HE HYPERVENTILATES
Benjamin?
OK. Breathe.
Breathe. In...
HE GASPS FOR BREATH
Breathe. It's OK, it's OK.
It's OK.
HIS BREATHING REGULATES
Breathe, that's it.
That's it. Keep going.
It's OK, it's OK.
It is? Is it?
Is it? Yeah, it's OK.
It's OK.
So, this evil plan of yours...
How can I help?
You keep your mum busy for the day.
Shopping, manicures,
or whatever mind-numbing activities
you girls enjoy.
Ow!
Your understanding of the
female species is second to none.
HE CHUCKLES
Then leave the rest to me.
BENJAMIN MOANS SOFTLY
BREATHING HEAVILY
HE GASPS
You all right?
Yeah.
I've, erm, been lying awake,
thinking about it.
Wanting to start over,
I do understand.
Forgive...
But I do need to know that's it.
There's nothing else.
I think anything else
would just destroy me.
I want to get to know Kieran.
Me too. Hm.
I think we should ask him
to stay here.
You're too good for this world,
you know that!
SHE SCOFFS
I think he said he's not
stopping though,
he's got some work on back home.
He'll be gone after the weekend.
So, let's ask him over,
make him feel welcome.
DOORBELL RINGS
Hey. These are for you.
Oh, they are so sweet. Go on in.
Eat. Please.
Otherwise I'll be inundating you
with questions
and everything will get cold.
Oh, fire away.
I hardly know where to start.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
This is a photo of the two of us
when we were bairns.
Don't judge the haircut.
You were blond? Blond-blond.
Hm. How many other things do
I not know about you, I wonder?
It was the day
after his tenth birthday,
he went dark overnight.
I mean, the fuss he made.
There were tears and everything.
Do you have any other photos?
Er, not many, but, yeah.
Back at the flat.
What, you're still...?
Yeah. I've given it a lick of paint.
Turned our room
into a weights room.
Sorry, you, er,
you weren't around to ask.
You'll have to come
and visit some time.
Oh, I'd love to!
See where you grew up.
What was he like as a child?
He was...
He was always in his own head.
Not like me, you know, I'll chat to
anyone. But my little brother,
he had these felt tips,
and they went, I'm not kidding,
they went everywhere with him.
I'd be playing football and look
over, he'd be no more than six,
writing stories
about King Arthur and dragons
and stuff I didn't know
anything about.
I knew then that he'd be somebody.
That he'd leave us behind.
LEO: Rolling back the years
over potted eggs?
Is there any other way?
I've got some for you in the Aga.
Oh, no. You carry on.
I just came to ask something.
Could I steal my mother
from you tomorrow?
You don't need to ask my permission.
He's a top man, your brother.
Should we hide the silver?
HE LAUGHS
It's a joke, Mum.
Remember that thing we used to do?
You're very...buoyant today.
What, I can't be excited to spend
the day with my mother?
Course you can.
I'm actually really pleased
that you suggested it.
I know that the last six months
haven't been exactly...
SHE SIGHS
Really, it should have been me
to...to make it right.
OK, I think we seriously need to
manage your expectations
of this day trip.
It's not some luxe spa.
Will you allow your old mum
a little sentiment?
It doesn't matter where we go,
I'd be happy with corned beef
sandwiches in the car,
so long as it's us two.
Aw.
We haven't been to
Becky Falls since you were kids.
Was this your idea? No.
No, this wasn't my idea.
Did you hear anything I said
the other day?
I did, actually.
Is there any reason that you're
both avoiding each other?
We're not avoiding each other.
There's no avoiding going on, son.
Good, then there's no reason
that you both can't spend the day
with me.
HE SIGHS
It's seriously slippy.
So, Dad, give Mum a hand up.
Oy! I'm not that ancient.
Don't be so stubborn.
SLIGHT CRY
SHE LAUGHS
HE LAUGHS
OK. Because I was in charge,
instead of chunks of already
browning apple...
Are you denigrating
my picnic skills?
..ta-da!
PHONE BEEPS
Oh, I haven't had
one of them in years.
The biscuit of champions.
Benjamin checking up on you, is he?
Mum, Rocky bar?
Oh, he's not checking up on me.
We just have a lot to sort
with the wedding.
Oh, of course,
the big day gallops ever nearer.
I haven't received my invite yet.
I've taken to
waiting by the postbox.
It's just a small affair.
I mean, really, it's a...
..it's a party.
To be honest, I didn't think
you'd want to come.
Why's that?
Surely someone's got to help me
with this caramel goodness?
In the spirit of playing
happy families...
Consider yourself invited.
We should head back,
we've got the meerkats at 3.00.
Obviously I'll require a plus-one.
For Marsha.
This isn't the first wedding
I've planned,
although this one differs,
because this time I'm actually
allowed to do what I want.
You had the wedding you wanted.
No, I had the wedding you wanted.
Sorry, dictated.
Which, let's be honest,
set the theme
for everything that followed,
didn't it?
Mum. Please.
Thank you, son.
Told you he was on my side.
I'm not on a side. Oh, so you didn't
pick your father's side
when you hid his affair from me?
Why did you tell her?
Because he wanted to hurt me.
And guess what, it worked.
Mum...
This was a bad idea.
Finally, we're agreed on something.
OK, look, we can reset.
I know we can. We just...
Take a few minutes out,
then wander back, feed the meerkats.
Enough with the bloody meerkats.
You're not five years old any more.
I didn't want to see anything.
I didn't want to know anything.
Believe me, Mum. I...
When I thought about telling you,
I just couldn't hurt you like that.
Dad swore he was going to fix things
with you. Make it how it was.
How it was?
How was it?
You were happy.
You and Dad.
And not in a grim
all-over-each-other way, just...
..working quietly.
It made me feel safe.
Like...our family
was the one solid thing.
But now?
We're being ripped apart...
..and it's all his fault.
Whatever you think went wrong, Leo,
it went wrong long before Benjamin.
PHONE DIALS
Mum and Dad,
they loved each other, didn't they?
Ease me into the conversation,
why don't you(!)
But they did.
I know they did. Didn't they?
Why don't you call Patrick?
He loves a deep-and-meaningful.
I'm not calling Patrick.
I'm calling you. OK.
It's just now's not a good time...
Say hello to my baby brother,
everyone.
I'm not your baby brother.
Oh, it's a term of affection,
numbnuts.
And also, I'm afraid,
factually correct.
What's up with you?
Nothing's up. Nothing.
I took Mum and Dad
to Becky Falls today.
Why the fuck would you do that?
What do you mean?
We used to have fun there.
By fun, do you mean that it
literally rained every time we went?
Dad kicking off about how expensive
the cream teas were,
so we'd end up driving back hungry,
one of us in tears.
Usually you. Actually, always you.
Why do you always do this,
you and Patrick,
make out like it
wasn't the way it was?
No, you're quite right,
we all held hands at Becky Falls,
made daisy chains and skipped
through the woods singing Kumba...
CALL ENDS
ELECTRONIC MUSIC
MUSIC DISTORTS
SIREN WAILS
They're both in.
Don't sweat it.
I was born stealthy.
How did it go?
Can we skip the talking?
Slow down.
What are you doing?
Stay. We can...watch a movie.
I don't want to watch a movie,
I want to have sex.
That is what young people do,
you know?
We're not some boring
middle-aged couple
with our cocoa and some boring
subtitled...
HE LAUGHS
We're not even a couple.
Why are you being so cruel?
What can I say? It comes naturally.
MARSHA: Cali? Have you got
someone in there?
What's wrong with the front door?
I was...helping Cali
with her job applications.
Your specialist subject.
SHE CLEARS THROAT
I'm just going to bounce.
Well, before you do, I'm sure you'll
be wanting to see your father.
Edward.
Don't you think you've caused
enough trouble today?
RAIN FALLS
MELANCHOLY MUSIC
INDISTINCT CHATTER
I guess, all being well,
you...you'll be my step-uncle.
Why are you fine with it,
him being with her?
You're seriously saying the age gap
doesn't bother you?
I'm just happy that he's happy.
However that looks.
Fuck. Fuckin' weird,
that's how it looks.
I mean, there's your brother...
..like some kind of poster boy...
..and then there's her. I mean,
she hardly in the shape of her life.
That's a nice way
to talk about your mum.
You look like
you're having a big one.
It's called having a drink.
Do you not have any mates?
I'm sorry. It's my bad.
Let me get a drink.
Same again please, love.
# You know that I will
never learn... #
You going to tell me, then,
why you really stopped speaking
to Benjamin
and why you're so different?
From the accent to...everything.
Different dads. Different schools.
Different mates.
And the 17-year big freeze?
I did some shitty things,
things that you should never do
to family. I lied, stole...
Great stock we're marrying into. No.
No, that's me.
That's not my brother.
Oh, because he's such
an upstanding guy.
Keeping you hidden away
like some dirty secret.
You know, I would forgive him almost
anything...because he's blood.
And in the end, that's all we have.
LAUGHTER
INDISTINCT SPEECH, LAUGHTER
That's the way to do it, lad.
HE SPITS
Can you not tell my mum about this?
Cold Chinese, a can of Coke,
you'll be sweet tomorrow.
Sounds grim.
And, remember, don't let my
little brother get you down.
He's not a bad guy.
Hey.
Another piece of advice, which you
can choose to completely ignore.
Don't make the same mistakes I did.
When I was your age...
..all I seemed to do
was prove people right about us.
Goodnight.
UPBEAT MUSIC
It should say,
"Leo and Kieran's Company,"
cos we're going to be partners.
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking, "What do
we do out of festival season?"
"What don't we do?"
would be the better question.
I'm actually quite impressed.
What, impressed like, "Well done"
or impressed like, "I'll invest?"
It's not a matter of trust.
I just wonder whether it
wouldn't be better for you
to earn the start-up capital
yourself.
And then your enthusiasm won't wane.
It won't. I'm serious about this.
Like you were serious
about surf school?
The bike rental app?
Your poetry nights?
OK, you're ridiculing me.
Don't ridicule me.
I'm not, darling.
I'm...I'm...I'm just trying...
You were going to say yes earlier,
I know you were.
And now, miraculously,
you've changed your mind.
You spoke to Benjamin, didn't you?
Of course I did. He's my fiance.
And he told you not to help me?
Because he wants all
your money for himself.
Because he can see
that by continuing to enable you,
I am doing you more harm than good.
Are you seriously
taking his word over mine?
Don't make this about Benjamin.
Everything's about Benjamin.
Everything's been about Benjamin
since the day you met.
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
All of my mates, all of them moved
straight in to London after uni,
into flats,
into having proper lives.
But I came back. For you.
You came back because it suited you.
Which is what you always do.
Ah. Right.
Right, so, you pretend to move out
so I give you what you want.
That's very mature.
I'm not pretending.
Don't be ridiculous.
Where are you even gonna go?
Where I'm wanted. Dad's.
Anywhere but there.
Please.
What would you care?
You've made it quite clear
that you only need one thing.
Benjamin.
MELANCHOLY MUSIC
I hope Benjamin's worth it.
INDISTINCT VOICES SPEAK
PATRICK: Benjamin shouldn't
have to call us.
I don't like being told about my own
mother by someone else.
But we're here now.
Look, you want Leo to move back,
I assume, which won't be easy...
..the way he is about Dad.
Unless...
If he knew...about that night.
We need biscuits.
If he knew, he'd come back.
It's time, Mum.
Time you stopped lying to him.
I've never lied.
I've just...not said.
And in the not saying,
you spare pain. Protect.
What's wrong with that?
So much, Mum.
All this silence,
this denial, it's a mind-fuck.
Not just for Leo,
who doesn't understand why things
are the way they are,
but for me, for us...
Don't speak for me.
What, you're really going to play
the well-adjusted card? A...
Fine, so it's just me, then,
turning it all over again and again,
thinking maybe it was a dream
or maybe I got it wrong
and I didn't see my dad
beat the shit out of my mum
and then try to kill himself?
There. I've said it.
And we didn't all combust.
I thought...
I thought you didn't remember.
You wanted us not to.
There's a difference.
Della, is he...? Do you...?
No. We're having this conversation.
Of course she remembers.
We were there together.
No.
You went to get Mum.
Left me on my own with...
..with him. And I didn't...
..I didn't do anything.
I didn't help.
SOBBING
I just...watched him.
Darling, you were only eight.
WEEPING
Conversation had.
Now, can I please be allowed
to stand the fuck up?
Dell.
You never said that.
How many times, Mum?
A Ryvita is not a biscuit!
I thought that
I was doing the right thing
by not talking about it.
And it was meant to keep you safe.
I'm so...
I didn't tell you all this
so you can feel bad.
I told you so that it could be
different for Leo.
I can't...
I can't do that to him.
His father is his whole world.
He's not a child any more.
None of us are.
We'll go and speak to him,
but if we could tell him...
..then Dad wins again.
TENSE MUSIC
MUSIC DISTORTS
How did you come by your injuries?
I've colleagues who can help.
BABY CRIES
I fell.
MUSIC FADES
Leo, he...he wasn't
in the listening mood.
You tried.
Does he know how much
he's upsetting her?
Yes, we equipped him
with the facts. Some of the facts.
All he had to say for himself was...
..he thinks you're exerting
undue influence
over our mother's finances.
He thinks?
Fine, I think.
We think you're marrying our mother
for her money.
Well, there it is...
..out in the open.
Don't say we didn't warn you.
Is everyone's family like this?
So I'm told.
It's hard to believe, isn't it?
CAR HORN BEEPS
You deserve to be happy, Mum.
CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS
HE TURNS MUSIC OFF
You're not upset with me, are you?
For interfering,
calling Patrick and Della?
It was nice.
Showed you cared.
You must never ever, ever doubt
that I care.
That's...insanity.
Are we OK?
We'd better be.
JULIA: I thought that organising
a dinner this close to the big day
was a kind of madness,
but maybe we can call this
a new start.
And if not quite that,
I hope at least a chance to practise
being civil to one another
before we're all on public display.
DELLA LAUGHS
Cheers, everyone. ALL: Cheers.
Patrick?
ALL: Cheers.
Are you sure
we shouldn't wait for Leo?
He knew the time, he knew
how important this was to you. Us.
His loss.
Oh, fuck. Sorry.
The gloves are on your shoulder.
I know. I'm an idiot.
DELLA: A lovable idiot.
Why, thank you.
Your glass is empty, my love,
which is entirely unacceptable.
You keeping me pickled
to get me down the aisle?
I'm onto you, Mr Greene.
Busted.
Patrick, would you mind grabbing us
another bottle?
They're just in the garage.
Well, we can't be low on champagne,
what with everything we have
to celebrate.
Thanks, mate.
SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
HAMMERING ON GLASS
Mum, I'm sorry,
but he's not a good man.
There are so many things that...
I will say this
one last time, Patrick.
Do not make me choose.
CAR PULLS UP
INDISTINCT CHATTER
DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES
Hey. Sorry to just pitch up. We...
It's just amazing you're here.
I thought you were heading home.
What can I say?
I couldn't stay away. Sit down.
So, have you guys eaten? No.
Do you want some moussaka?
Yeah, that'd be great. Thanks.
Please.
I'll be right back.
Kieran.
Thank you.
No problem. I like Leo.
He's a good lad.
Me too.
Hey, bro, listen.
I've got some really good news and
I wanted to tell you in person.
Tell me what?
Leo's dad's agreed to back
his venture...
..which means I've got myself a job.
A job where?
Here, of course.
I hoped it'd give us a chance to...
..properly get to know each
other again.
What are you doing?
I want us to elope.
Imagine it, just us. We...we can
have the wedding the way that we
want it, and then we can go,
we can hole up in your villa
and...and we can try...
we can get back to way
that things were when we...
when we first met.
This is...odd behaviour.
Well, I prefer impulsive.
Our wedding is in two days,
Benjamin. Two days.
Everything is ready,
all the money's been spent.
I thought...I thought you didn't
care about money?
That's not what this is about.
This is about Kieran coming back.
No, it's not. There's something
that you're not saying.
And I'm not an idiot,
despite the fact that everyone seems
to treat me like one.
OK.
OK, I...I sat around that table
tonight and I thought...
..I thought, "Who here is
actually happy for us?"
And I...I...I have kept hoping
that...that...that by the time
that we got married,
that there would be...
HE SIGHS
..that things would change.
That there would be, I
don't...if not love for us...
..me, that there would be,
I don't know, at least good will.
But there's just...
There's just not.
So. You and me. Hm?
What do you say?
I'd say it sounds a lot
like running away.
One more sleep.
Apart.
I didn't think you were
being serious.
I'm afraid so.
Separate beds for the bride and
groom the night before or else...
..terrible things will befall us.
HE SCOFFS
ENGINE STARTS
TENSE MUSIC
PHONE RINGS
Hello.
DELLA: Mum! Where are you?
You've been gone for hours.
Benjamin's been calling.
We're not supposed to speak
before the wedding.
Right. Tell him that.
And tell him I'm there with you.
OK. But you're not.
Then lie, Della.
I'm sure that's not beyond you.
What? What's going on, Mum?
Something is going on.
I know it is.
Mum?
You don't know a
Benjamin Greene, do you?
He used to live across the road
on the Chethurst estate?
Benjamin Greene?
No, I can't say I do.
And I like to think
I know most folks 'round here.
Do you know Kieran Marshall,
his brother?
Oh, Kieran. Oh, aye.
Everyone knows Kieran.
But his brother's called Sean.
Look, er...
This is Benjamin.
Well, bugger me!
Who is he to you?
I'm marrying him tomorrow.
After what he did?
DRAMATIC MUSIC
BENJAMIN: Marriage is forever.
It's being able to
say, "What's mine is yours
"and what's yours is mine."
If you tell Eimear,
I swear I will kill you.
It's us. It's always been us.