Traduçao por Robson = KillerBee
Um veredicto surpreendente em que muitos estão chamando
o julgamento de assassinato mais controverso nos últimos anos.
Anthony Tucker considerado culpado de assassinato em primeiro grau.
Meu cliente mantém sua inocência.
Nós não temos nenhum comentário neste momento.
Como você pôde fazer isso com sua esposa?
Anthony Tucker, tenho a honra de convidá-lo formalmente
para participar como um concorrente neste ano de
Jogos Jurássico.
Você aceita?
Sim.
Em notícias de entretenimento, os concorrentes deste ano
para os Jogos Jurássico foram escolhidos.
Eu nem sequer se preocupam com os concorrentes,
Eu quero ver o anfitrião quente e que ele vai estar vestindo
e dizendo, isso é o que eu quero ver.
Ooh, eu não posso esperar!
Ele parece real, não é?
A areia em sua pele.
O sol em seu rosto, o sabor em sua boca.
Well to all of you this world is absolutely real.
The danger is real and the pain is real.
But so is the reward.
Oh, oh, be careful with that.
I'll need you to do as I say or boom.
You all know that when you die in here,
you die for real.
All of you are in here for one reason.
To win your freedom.
To go home.
You can avoid the death you justly deserve by surviving,
by fighting, by confronting your fears
and proving your worthiness.
Your goal is to be the sole survivor.
Find yourself the last man or woman standing
and you will win a full pardon, you will go home,
free, alive, exonerated.
Now it will be tempting to kill each other,
there's no rules against that,
but please if you would be so kind,
try to leave at least some of you alive
for the main attraction.
Oh, did you feel that?
A few miles beyond the tree-line
your first objective awaits.
A temporary safe zone.
Now your collars will alert you when you arrive.
Red, you're too far away, yellow means
you're getting closer, and green means you have reached
the safe zone and completed your first challenge.
Reach the safe zone in one hour or you die.
Die here in the game and as you know
you will die in real life by lethal injection
as been assigned by the state.
The pain you feel in this world will be real pain.
Like the real pain you inflicted
on those that you have killed.
Everyone understand?
Good.
Congratulations to you all.
As of right now, you are no longer death row inmates.
You are contestants on the greatest game show in the world,
the Jurassic Games!
Oh shit.
Did I mess up my hair?
No, it's good?
Okay.
Alright guys, you ready?
How long until we're live?
Live in 10.
Okay.
Alright everyone, we're going live in three, two...
They have less than 59 minutes to reach the safe zone.
So sit back, try to relax and enjoy, ladies and gentlemen.
Because today is going to be a hell of a day
for our brave contestants.
So far so good.
I mean that lineup is gorgeous on camera.
I'm telling you right now we are hitting
all the key demographics.
It's a great cast.
It's the best one yet.
Stay on the cannibal.
Stay outta my way, you piece of shit!
I'm sorry!
Please don't hurt me, please!
This is real!
I can taste you!
Our contestants are frantically
trying to find the safe zone.
Don't worry, I'm sure most of them will.
But in the end, nine will die and one will win.
And this year's four stages are by far the best ever.
Stage one.
The contestants must survive being hunted by hungry dinosaurs
long enough to find the temporary safe zone.
Stage two.
The maze.
A deadly labyrinth filled with some of our fan favorites.
That's right, the raptors are back this year.
Stage three, the minefield.
Tread lightly and you might walk out of this game
with all your limbs.
And our final stage this year?
You don't actually think I'm gonna give that away, do you?
Let's just say you won't be disappointed.
So stay tuned, fans!
Because the Jurassic Games start right now!
In the ultimate reality game show,
10 death row inmates must survive a virtual world
filled with the deadliest predators to ever roam the earth.
William Davis, guilty on 23 counts of drug-related homicide.
Ren Saizo, contract killer.
Guilty of the murder of a United States senator.
Victor Gonzalez, The Wasp.
Leader of the Hive drug cartel.
Guilty of 35 counts of murder.
Stephanie Rogers...
Brian, status report.
Games on alpha online, raptor AI online,
prepping game zone beta, prepping to disengage rex one.
Security holding up?
Airtight.
46 attempts to breach our firewall
but so far none successful.
And none will be.
Stay vigilant.
Back live in the studio in 10.
Okay.
We never know who, we never know when.
But sadly we had to say goodbye to Dr. Eli Franklin.
The first contestant to be eliminated
in this year's Jurassic Games.
Of course, we can't feel too sorry for him.
That guy liked to blow people up.
A lot.
What's going on with Dr. Franklin?
Dr. Franklin?
You okay?
God, he's so weird.
Hey wait, doc, you forgot your bag!
I don't know about you, but honestly
he wasn't one of my favorites anyway.
Only nine contestants remain.
Do you know where the safe zone is?
I'm lost.
You're next, bitch!
What?
You're kind of a pussy, aren't you?
I'm not here to kill anybody.
I'm here to kill everybody.
Well, not you.
Not yet.
Lighten up.
Come on, I think the safe zone's this way and I'm scared.
No more games!
No more...
Live in three, two.
Thank you.
I'm here with Bailey and Andrew Tucker.
Thank you for taking the time to meet with me.
Bailey, let's start with you, sweetheart.
How do you feel about your father
being a contestant on the Jurassic Games?
Um, this was his only chance to get out, so.
That's right.
If he wins, he will be pardoned of all of his crimes.
He didn't commit any crimes.
And he didn't kill my mom!
Andrew stop, we're not supposed to talk about it.
It's alright.
Your mother's death was tragic.
I'm very sorry she can't be with you here today.
Thank you.
Is there anything you'd like to say to your father?
Look into this camera.
You can send him a message.
Survive, Dad, please.
We know you're innocent.
Get him out of the games!
- Stop the games! - Andy.
No more games!
I can't believe they made me talk to his kids.
They think he's innocent.
What difference does it make?
Well, what if they found proof?
You think they'd let him go?
If they find proof, we'll never hear about it.
Trust me.
Let's go!
Move, move, move!
So how close are they?
The audience is getting restless.
A few minutes most, but they're good hunters.
I thought we could build tension.
Build tension?
Our viewers don't care about tension, Brian.
They just wanna see the contestants die horribly.
Spawn them closer next time.
And stay on Tucker.
The audience already is sympathetic with him.
Let's watch him die live.
You got it.
So your wife.
She was tortured.
Leave it alone.
I wonder what she was thinking when she died.
Some people can just turn it off.
The pain.
I've always admired that.
I read your cast bio.
Loving daddy, good man.
It's clear why the world thinks you're innocent.
If it makes you feel any better, I believe you.
Goodie.
Get up!
I'll see you in the next round.
Go you little bitch.
Hey, you know what?
Can we get some wind, just to make him sway
a little bit?
Roll her package.
Bloodthirsty.
Merciless.
Psychopath.
Words used to describe Sarah Laforte.
The youngest death row inmate
to ever enter the Jurassic Games.
I had the opportunity to sit down with her
and try to get inside the head of this cold-blooded killer.
Sarah?
I just want to ask you a few questions.
Joy.
My friends call me Joy.
Why do you prefer to be called Joy?
Because I'm such a happy person.
Okay Joy.
What happened in your life that brought you here
at such a young age?
It's a secret.
Any more questions?
Ah, well well well.
You are still hanging in there, aren't ya?
Oh come on man, come on!
What do you got inside ya, huh?
Are you gonna let this little girl
take you out of the game this early?
What about your kids?
You can't die now.
Jesus.
We must work together as long as we can.
There are things more terrible than us in this game.
As individuals, we don't stand a chance!
There may still be a way to escape
if we work together.
We must get to the safe zone.
We are being hunted.
There are three of them.
We must go, now!
You're not planning on using that, are you?
No.
We wouldn't want an uprising.
It almost sounds like you do.
His children, Savannah?
You made me interview Tucker's children?
Well he's trending high.
People want him to win.
It's been a while since we had one that might be innocent.
His children believe that he is,
and they're about to see him
get ripped to shreds on live TV.
Nobody's forcing you to be here.
There are a number of people behind you that would
love your job.
Younger, smarter, prettier.
They would put their first born in the game
to get a shot at your position.
I know.
I want to be here.
Good.
Oh.
If you ever question an assignment again,
you can go ahead and clean out your desk.
Oh he should be easy.
You want him?
Wait.
Don't be stupid.
Hi friend.
Do you happen to know which way it is to the safe zone?
We don't have much time to find it.
No, I have no idea.
We're lost.
We could die on the first challenge.
Wrong answer, pal!
Wait, stop!
The raptors have entered the canyon area.
What?
No, no no no.
How long until they get to them?
Any second now.
Do you know who I am?
I am El Avispa, The Wasp!
You know who I am?
I'm The Wasp!
I got a big stinger on my butt
and when I sting you I'm gonna die.
I think that's a bee, man.
Shut up!
I have very powerful friends.
Friends who can help us.
Help me.
Help me get to the end, help me win.
Why would we do that?
Because I can save your mother.
What do you know about my mama, huh?
I know all about you.
Trust me.
I can get us all out of here.
You will be able to see your mother again.
Alive and well.
You sack of shit!
Wait wait wait wait wait!
Well?
What are you waiting for?
Wait wait wait.
Not yet.
Come on!
What the?
What is happening in here?
Our ratings have dipped 4%.
Why did you stop the raptors?
Listen, it's called foreplay, Savannah.
You might wanna try it sometime.
Alright we're back in five, four, three, two.
That just happened.
Could this be an unholy alliance
between the Mason brothers and The Wasp?
That would be a match made in hell.
And ladies and gentlemen, I would hate to see
what that means for our other contestants.
Let's head back to the canyon.
What just happened?
Let's go.
Wait!
Join me.
Help me get to the end.
I can save your mother, I promise.
Come on.
You really think he's gonna save anybody else but himself?
How stupid could you be?
She's dying of cancer, no?
No one dies of cancer anymore.
Poor people do, you piece of shit!
I can pay for the treatment!
Okay, okay, okay!
We'll help you.
Have you lost your mind?
Haven't you seen this show before?
If he wins, we die, you idiot!
No he said he could get us out too, huh?
He knows people, right?
Si.
If there's even a chance that we can save Mom.
This is all bullshit!
If he knows anyone outside, then what's he doing
in here in the first place?
I want you to use your tiny little brain.
Think about that, ya moron.
God damnit!
God damnit, what?
You touch him, and I'll kill you myself.
Okay, fine!
Fine!
For now.
We'll help.
None of them know.
Unfortunately, their mother, Rosetta Mason, passed yesterday.
Such tragedy.
But I promise that you are gonna see the raptors soon
because stage two, the maze, is up next
right here on the Jurassic Games.
And we're clear.
That was a good transition, right?
That was good.
Nice work.
I at first felt that the brothers angle was a little forced
but it was good drama.
Well, alright.
Hey, by the way, we gotta make sure we keep them alive
as long as possible.
Okay, can you imagine a Cane and Abel type of ending
for the finale?
I'm sorry to interrupt, the contestants
are approaching the safe zone right now.
We are close!
Keep going!
Objective complete.
Safe zone activated.
Go ahead.
Taste some.
I don't think they'd let you die of poison berry.
That's not very exciting.
Seems like everything in here tastes a little bit better.
I don't know how they do it.
Do you?
How would you taste?
Objective complete.
Safe zone activated.
What a surprise.
I'm Tucker, I'm innocent.
I'm Albert and I'm gonna eat you.
Jurassic Games action figures.
Available wherever fine toys are sold.
Tucker.
Joy.
Dr. Franklin.
Billy.
Big Brother.
Little Brother.
Stephanie.
Ren.
Collect all 10 contestants today.
And if you collect all 10 action figures
of this year's contestants, we will throw in
the brand new version of yours truly.
Complete with 10 new catchphrases.
That's right, the raptors are back this year.
Get yours now while supplies last.
Every single network is covering the games.
This is even bigger than last year.
Looks like a riot in Midtown.
Eh, nothing new.
They've been protesting for years.
Yeah.
We should put some of those Cavemen in the games.
Yeah no shit.
Come on.
We're starting the maze.
No more games, no more games, no more games!
Only eight remain.
What a cast though, huh?
The Mason brothers.
Would you take out one of your own
if it really came down to it?
We'll see.
We got Joy.
Ah, Joy, Joy, Joy.
I'm telling you, there is something special
about sweet little Joy.
Then we got Albert, the cannibal.
Albert, you make me sick.
In a good way, of course, because people tune in
just to see you die.
I like you.
Keep you around for our international viewers.
And then we have poor Anthony Tucker.
Doesn't really seem like he's cut out for this,
but you know what, America loves a tragic hero so I do too.
Hang in there, buddy.
Stephanie.
Oh Stephanie.
I'd really hate for someone or something
to ruin that pretty face.
Guess we'll have to wait for that.
And El Avispa, The Wasp.
I like you.
You're naughty.
Alright, wake 'em up, I wanna play.
Welcome, contestants.
I hope you are ready for your first challenge.
We like to call it the maze.
A favorite segment of the games
and our longest-running challenge.
The rules are simple.
Be the first to escape your chains
and you will be awarded this.
Right?
Use it to protect yourself,
use it to obliterate your enemies.
The choice is yours.
I think in the right hands, the hands of a fighter,
the hands of a winner, this fine piece of hardware
could wind up ending the game early.
Anything can happen in the Jurassic Games.
That's what makes it so much fun!
So here we go!
Ready in three two one go!
I got it!
You're all dead!
I win!
Game over!
Albert, Albert!
You have no honor if you use that now against us.
Shut up!
Anybody else, any last words?
Please, please don't shoot, I was kidding.
- I won't kill anybody. - Stay still!
Please!
Shoot him, what are you waiting for?
He's not gonna shoot him.
He's the perfect person for the gun.
The one that won't use it.
Move away.
Ren.
Go, go!
Go!
- There's not an exit. - What?
There's not a way out, they're all dead ends.
That way!
Where's Ren?
- Who? - The grate.
Get back!
Go, hurry, go!
Go!
Move!
Watch out!
We're right back where we started.
Congratulations, contestants.
Well done.
Stephanie.
Because you were the first to exit the maze
I am gonna reward you with this.
And not far from here you will find a crate
containing a few potentially game-changing supplies.
This map will help you get there safely.
Stephanie, you may choose to share it
or keep it to yourself.
The clock is ticking, contestants.
Give it to me!
Hey back off!
I want that.
Hey, let her go!
Get off me, boy.
I got it.
Come on.
Let's go.
Like that?
How does that feel?
First thought to have been a hoax,
Stephanie Rogers brutally murdered 16 men
and broadcast her kills live on the internet.
She spent the last three years
at the Starkweather Federal Penitentiary
prior to her acceptance in this year's Jurassic Games.
She'll use her charms to seduce the men in the game,
just like a black widow luring them into her trap,
killing them in cold blood.
Gimme a break.
Come with me.
I have to do some fluff piece interview.
I'm joined now by Savannah Black.
She is the director of the controversial sensation
known around the globe as the Jurassic Games.
Savannah, thank you for joining us this afternoon.
Oh, my pleasure Jack, thank you for having me.
Let's begin right off the bat
with the morality issue here.
Uh, excuse me?
Well you know as well as anybody
the show is controversial, even still.
Are we still discussing this?
The contestants on our show are going to die anyway.
Now what we're doing, with the support of the government,
I might add, is giving them a chance at freedom.
But some say this is too much.
Isn't this really nothing more than exploitation
of these contestants for money, for ratings?
And you are essentially torturing them on live television.
Well I'm not concerned with a vocal minority.
A lot more people love the games.
300 million the last time I looked.
It's what the people want.
You didn't answer my question.
Well they are still dying by lethal injection.
- Yes, but... - Listen.
We didn't invent this.
As much as I'd like to take credit for it,
public execution is nothing new.
Think back to the days of the Roman Empire.
The gladiators fought tigers and there was
a Coliseum filled with people wanting the tiger to win
and most often it did.
Now at least on our show one of our contestants
is guaranteed to live.
What about Anthony Tucker?
There are a lot of folks out there who believe
he was wrongly convicted of killing his wife.
Well he was convicted in a court of law
and sentenced to death.
And that is the only qualification required
to enter the games.
Oh, that and they look good on camera.
But wouldn't you agree having an innocent contestant
killed on your show does nothing more than fuel the fire
for groups like The Cavemen?
I'm not familiar with them.
You're trying to tell me you've never heard
of The Cavemen?
I am aware of a very few and extremely disorganized...
Come on, it's well-known they have promised
to disrupt the ending of this year's games.
Surely you're aware.
Well groups like that have tried before.
But our security is tight, and I am confident
that the games will go on as they always do.
Now we are approaching our next challenge
and your audience won't wanna miss that.
Savannah Black, thank you for joining us.
Oh, thank you Jack.
Asshole!
Volunteering for the games is an admission of guilt!
These aren't people, they're murderers.
God, I've had it up to here with The Cavemen.
People have a right to protest.
Okay, protesting is one thing
but threatening to disrupt the show's ending,
whatever the hell that's supposed to mean, is unacceptable.
You don't like the show?
Well neither do I, and do you know why?
Because there's a winner.
One of these lunatics gets to walk away free.
And it makes me sick.
If it were up to me they'd all be dead already.
That thing is huge.
So why did you enter the lottery?
Same reason as everybody.
Freedom.
You really didn't do it, did you?
That's what I heard.
Doesn't matter much now, does it?
Why do you think they picked dinosaurs
to be the things we're running away from?
It tested better than robots.
Look I dunno man, gimme the map.
You don't even know how to operate it.
I don't give a damn, gimme the map!
Kiss my ass!
Help me!
He's gonna die anyway, leave his ass.
No, he's gonna finish, he's gonna make it.
This is it for me.
I was never gonna help you anyway, you piece of shit.
Your mom's gonna follow me to hell.
It's nothing.
Calm down!
I'm not playing this game anymore.
I'm done!
You hear me?
I quit!
- Put me back in my cell... - Hey!
I'm not playing this game anymore!
Hey!
It's you and me!
We gotta stay together, focus!
You focus.
Focus.
Well you didn't see that coming, did ya?
Our contestants are tired, they're hungry.
The Wasp is gone, but I have a feeling it's about to get
a whole lot tougher for our remaining six.
And we're clear.
How close are they to the supplies?
They're approaching right now.
The buzzards are circling.
Welcome, contestants, and congratulations on your success
and survival.
We're down to the final six but we seem to be missing one.
Ah, there she is.
The odds-on favorite to win.
I'm gonna kill you.
I sincerely doubt it.
Beyond the red barrier you will find two items
that may be of some use to you.
A knife, and, more importantly, some more ammunition
for your laser gun there.
All you have to do is just walk from here to there.
There are 17 mines...
Uh, well, maybe 20, I can't remember.
Between you and your reward.
Don't worry.
Stephanie's map will guide you through.
Use it to survive.
Stop the game, I'm not going through!
Stop it!
Come on!
What are you doing?
Come on brother, come on through, come on.
No, no, come on!
Come on, no, no!
No, god damnit!
No!
Shit!
My brother's dead!
Back off, bitch.
Who's the odds-on favorite now?
Well there goes Cain and Abel.
I'm not gonna do another interview like that,
not during the games.
That was an ambush.
Hey, look at these ratings though.
Look at 'em.
And nice work, by the way, Brian, with the pterodactyl.
I gotta say, I am really happy with our final four.
You know Jack mentioned a direct threat from The Cavemen.
He said they're threatening to disrupt
the ending of the show.
Oh, The Cavemen.
What are they going to do Savannah, huh?
What are they gonna do?
Every year they say the same shit.
Every year nothing happens except for what?
More controversy.
Controversy leads to excitement, more excitement leads to
more viewers.
Hell, I love The Cavemen.
Status report.
Four remaining contestants are relatively close
to each other.
Shut down most of the main systems
while I load the traps and weather simulation.
You what, hey, hey.
Why don't you let 'em breathe for a minute?
Never know.
Maybe one of the girls'll get naked.
She's watching us, you know.
Maybe you oughta give me that clip.
Come and get it.
I'd go look for her but I don't wanna leave you alone.
With him.
Smart man.
You move one inch closer to me and I'll gut you.
Alright.
It's fine.
You're not much older than my daughter.
I was asleep.
And I heard a noise and I went downstairs.
And the door had been pried open.
And I went to the kids' rooms and I made sure
they were okay, they were sleeping.
And then I went back to my room.
And I found my wife with her throat slit.
She was covered in blood and her eyes were wide open.
The murder weapon was a knife from my kitchen
and they said that I had pried the door open myself
to make it seem like a home invasion.
And I was convicted and I was sentenced.
You're just a kid.
I'm gonna take you to the final two
and I'm gonna kill you.
Tucker!
I know you're close!
Ladies and gentlemen, it's come to my attention
that one of our witnesses would like to share something
with us.
He killed someone close to you, didn't he?
My husband.
And now you feel like you finally have some closure.
Yes, yes I do.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
That is a natural feeling.
And we all understand.
We're very close to finding out
who will win this year's games.
Don't go away.
Holy shit, who is this?
Whoa, the best actress award goes to,
what was your name, sweetie?
- Alison. - Alison.
Give it up for Alison.
She almost had me crying.
Can you believe that?
We need more of her, seriously.
Find out whoever her acting class was.
I'm gonna go get a drink, I'm a little emotional.
My kids.
If you can hear me.
I love you.
I'm coming home.
Dad!
Do you hear that?
I'm coming home!
You're not looking so good.
You're the one that's gonna kill me?
Oh honey, you're already dead.
We're getting immense pressure from the press
to comment on Tucker's innocence.
Okay, well here's my comment to the press.
He was sentenced to death.
Okay we have run the numbers
and it could be a ratings disaster if he dies in the game.
Are you out of your mind?
What do you want?
You know what?
Come to me live as soon as the tiger's finished.
Only two remain.
Joy, the heartless teenage killer, ruthless and crazy.
Who knows why, who cares?
And Tucker, a family man who callously murdered his wife
in cold blood.
Presumed innocent by some of you.
Listen to me.
I am not the judge.
We are not the jury.
But the game.
The game is the executioner.
And the game decides who lives and who dies.
Uh oh, we've got a problem.
We just received an encrypted message.
From The Cavemen?
No, from here, inside the premises.
Open the final doorway.
The last challenge begins now.
I told you!
I told you I'd bring you to the final two with me!
Excuse me, I need to get to master control.
Sit down.
We've intercepted an encoded transmission coming from
- the premises. - Really?
What did it say?
We don't know.
I was hoping you could tell me.
We traced the transmission back to your edit bay, Laura.
Have you been sending encoded messages?
I'm going to kill The Host.
On live TV.
Tonight.
No matter what you do, the show will continue.
It's bigger than me, than you, than anyone!
You'll never...
Let's do this.
Patience, Tucker.
Joy, you are the favorite to win this thing, you know.
Eat shit!
That's the spirit.
Tucker, I'm not sure anyone expected you to get this far
but there are millions of people rooting for you out there.
In fact, we have a very special message from your kids.
Survive, Dad, please.
We know you're innocent.
Get him out of the games.
- Stop the games! - Andy.
Bring 'em back.
Bring 'em back, bring 'em back!
Bring 'em back to me!
Ow!
Why so upset?
We are giving you a chance to see them again.
I mean really if it wasn't for our little show here,
you'd already be dead.
And let the final challenge begin.
Well, this is an easy game.
Now you will notice that you are each chained
to those locks.
There are padlocks at the end of your chains
that need to be unlocked for you to cross the outer
finish line.
Be the first to do so, and your opponent will be eliminated.
You win!
The keys.
Excuse me?
I don't think I quite caught that.
Where are the keys to unlock the padlocks?
There are two.
One for each of you.
Buried in the sand somewhere between
where you stand and the locks.
Are you ready in three, two, one, go!
Tucker.
Do you know why I threw in my name for the games?
I don't care about my freedom.
Hell, being in here is as close as I could ever hope
to being free.
A girl that does things that I do won't last very long
in the real world anyway, you know?
I wanted to meet you!
Convicted killer that the whole world loves.
The man that wanted to join the games
so he could see his precious kids again.
The man that everyone cried over
when his sentence was given.
I mean what the hell?
You talk too much.
She cried for you.
She missed you.
She said that you were gonna come save her
and I really wish you would have because I was
so tired of waiting.
I'm here to finish what I started!
I can't let the whole world see you go free!
I'm gonna cause one more moment of chaos and heartbreak
before I leave this disgusting world!
I killed your bitch of a wife and I would do it again
and again and again
if I could!
Yes.
Yes, this is perfect, this is perfect.
This is awesome!
You knew?
Well, I mean, you know, we hoped.
See you in hell, you piece of shit!
What did you say to me?
I said I killed your wife.
Uh, give me a rex.
Bring in a rex.
I said I killed her, ah!
I'm gonna kill you.
Where, Savannah!
We need a rex.
Will you just, where is she?
Do I have to do everything myself?
Just bring it out.
Savannah!
Come on.
Oh God, get out of the way!
Let's have some fun, shall we?
What are they doing, why aren't they attacking them?
We programmed them to behave the same way
that they would in nature and they're very territorial.
We've never had this many at once
so I don't know what they're gonna do.
Well then fix it!
Oh shit!
Yes!
- Pull him out now. - What?
Whoa, whoa, Laura, what are you doing?
Wake him up, slowly.
Brian, go to commercial, right now.
No Brian, bring it here, now.
Laura, look at me, look at me.
This has to be some kind of a misunderstanding.
The game is over for good.
Okay.
Where's Savannah?
Savannah!
This has gone on long enough!
Tonight this is over.
There will be no more Jurassic Games.
Okay, Laura, what are you, stop, what are you doing?
This is crazy.
Jeff.
Are you serious?
I've known you 10 years.
Are you kidding me?
What is happening right now, are you crazy?
You're going in.
What?
No!
Stop!
Stop it right now!
Stop it!
Brian.
If I don't call off that T-Rex, it will kill him.
You're not gonna shoot me.
Bring it to me live, now.
It's over, everyone.
It's over.
Now watch this evil piece of shit learn his lesson.
Back to the desert.
Do it!
Okay.
Alright.
Come on baby, make it good.
Let's fucking go!
We all know by now
os terríveis acontecimentos que ocorreram
durante o final desta temporada passada dos Jogos Jurássico.
Pessoas de todo o mundo ainda estão de luto
a morte do amado host.
Foi trágico, com certeza.
Mas, você sabe o que eles dizem.
O show tem que continuar!
Espere, o que você está dizendo?
Sabe alguma coisa que nós não sabemos?
Nós temos o exclusivo sobre os todos os novos jogos Jurássico.
De volta e melhor do que nunca para a próxima temporada.
Isso é tão emocionante!
Todos os novos concorrentes, um novo hospedeiro, e temos algo
muito especial para mostrar a você.
Um clipe exclusivo de algumas das estrelas do show
ostentando algumas surpreendentes novas atualizações.
Ooh, eu não posso esperar!
Rolar o clipe.
Obrigado por assistir conosco smartflix.com